SATYAJIT MONDAL

Full Stack Software Developer Portfolio: satyajitmondal.com
Contact: +8801917801124

E-mail: satyajit.cse@yahoo.com

Skype: live:satyajit.cse

Address: Mirpur-1, Dhaka 1216

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I'm an experienced full stack software developer who has built and scaled user focused web applications and services. I'm also passionate about build things, solve problems, agile methodologies, and collaboration techniques that help multidisciplinary teams grow and build better product.

KEY SKILLS

I've worked with multiple technologies so far like

- HTML5 - Laravel

- CSS3 - Vue js

- JavaScript(ES6+) - Nuxt js

- MySQL - Node js

- PHP - Linux

- AWS - Docker

EDUCATION

- B.Sc (Hons) in Computer Science and Engineering

Daffodil International University

Batch: 40TH, (2015-2018)

CGPA: 3.09 out of 4.0

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

- Certified in Web Application Development-PHP

BITM (Basis Institute of Technology & Management)

Batch: PHP-72, (15/11/2017 to 17/02/2018)

EMPLOYMENT

August 2021 - Present

Software Engineer | SWAP | Dhaka

- Refactoring existing code to ensure the quality of products are maintained over time. (<u>Live Preview</u>)
- Responsible for defining deployment strategies for cloud (**AWS**) and on premise deployment for different projects. Responsible for deployment of couple of projects.
- Analyzing requirements and making budget estimation for new projects.

<u>January 2020 – July 2021</u>

Software Engineer | Netcoden Canada | Dhaka

- Lead two medium size of project in a row, Trading-Learning-Platform(T4T) and another one is Drop-shipping.
- Develop and maintain the Forexcrm.ca that a Customer relationship management(CRM) by multiple backend language (https://tinyurl.com/satyajitmondal)
- Integrate different kinds of international payment gateway to collect payments and support SAAS based software <u>forex-crm</u>.

February 2019 - December 2019

Full Stack Software Developer | Regfire Solutions LTD | Dhaka

- Developed a web application Human Resource Management (HRM) from scratch for code-canyon marketplace.
- Develop and maintain a live web application Point of Sale (POS) of codecanyon marketplace.(Live Preview)

January 2017 - January 2019

Full Stack Software Developer | Freelance | Dhaka

- Designed and developed custom websites and web applications
- Collaborated and worked iteratively with clients to determine necessary project requirements.

PERSONAL INTERESTS

Biking | Traveling | Badminton | Reading | Cooking

REFERENCES

References are available on request.